http://www.whittier.edu/terms-of-use

Search whittier.edu
All Departments3-2 Engineering ProgramAboutAcademic AffairsAcademicsAdmissionAdvancementAdvancing STEM Academic ProgramAfricana & Black StudiesAll Offices & ServicesAnthropologyArt & Visual StudiesASWCAthleticsBe You. Dream Big.BiologyBusiness AdministrationBusiness OfficeCalendarCampus SafetyCampus TechnologyCareer and Professional DevelopmentCenter for Advising and Academic SuccessCenter for Engagement with CommunitiesChemistryCommencementCommuter StudentsConference ServicesCounseling CenterCOVID-19 ResponseDean of StudentsDepartment of HistoryDepartment of PhilosophyDesign & Digital Media Training HubEconomicsEducation and Child DevelopmentEducator Professional DevelopmentEmerging Media IncubatorEnglish Language and LiteratureEnvironmental SciencesEnvironmental StudiesFacility ServicesFaculty-in-ResidenceFellowshipsFilm StudiesFinancial AidFirst-Year ExperienceFrench Cultural StudiesGarrett HouseGender StudiesGlobal and Cultural StudiesGo Poets!Graduate Programs in EducationGreenleaf Art GalleryHartley HouseHealth CenterHHMIHousing & Residential LifeHuman ResourcesInauguration of Linda OubréInitiatives on InnovationInnovation at WhittierInstitute for Baseball StudiesInstitute for Culturally and Linguistically Responsive TeachingInstitutional ResearchIntegrated Computer ScienceInternshipsKinesiologyLatino StudiesLiberal Education ProgramLuce Initiative on Asian Studies and the EnvironmentMail & Print CenterMathematics & Computer ScienceMilitary & Veteran AffairsModern Languages & LiteraturesMusicNewsOffice of Equity & InclusionOffice of International ProgramsOffice of Marketing & CommunicationsOffice of Marketing & CommunicationsOffice of Student EngagementOffice of the PresidentOrganizational LeadershipOrientationOrtiz ProgramsPhysics & AstronomyPoet HomecomingPoet NationPoliciesPolitical SciencePre-Professional ProgramsPsychological SciencesPublic HealthRegistrar's OfficeReligious StudiesResearch & Sponsored ProgramsResearch Ethics & Safety ComplianceScientific ComputingShannon CenterSocial WorkSociologyStrategic PlanningStudent Disability ServicesStudent EmploymentStudent LifeThe Big Poet GiveTheatre & Communication ArtsTransforming LivesURSCAVP of Academic AffairsWardman LibraryWellness CoalitionWhittier NEXTWhittier Scholars ProgramWriting Program
Mobile Main Navigation - Admission
Admission
Open
Make Your Deposit
First-Year Students
Transfer Students
International Students
Reactivating an Application
Terms of Use
Whittier College (“Whittier” or “the College”) provides this website (“site”) as a service to students, faculty, alumni, and prospective students. Use of the site is subject to the terms and conditions set forth below in Whittier's Privacy Policy (“policy”). This policy is provided in accordance with the California Business and Professions Code, Section 22575-22579.
Policy
Whittier is committed to protecting the privacy and accuracy of your personally identifiable information to the fullest extent possible, subject to provisions of state and federal law. Other than in response to subpoenas or other legal instruments that authorize disclosure, personally identifiable information is not disclosed without your consent to nonaffiliated third party vendors.
Information Collection and Use
Categories of personally identifiable information collected by webpages managed or maintained by Whittier College or by other entities affiliated with Whittier College, may include: your Internet location (Internet domain and IP address), type of browser and operating system used to access our site, date and time our site was visited, pages visited on our site, search terms used on our search engines, along with information you use to fill out forms such as: name, e-mail address, address, birthday, college ID number, social security number, credit card number, and Whittier ID. This personally identifiable information is used to respond to user inquiries or processing transactions.
In order to keep you informed of such activities as campus programs, symposia and/or special events, we may use personal information collected from webpages for the purpose of future communication back to online enrollees. Such e-mail notification will be conducted in conformance with the federal anti-spam law.
Additionally, the web server may collect, at least temporarily, the following information: Internet Protocol (IP) address of computer being used; webpages requested; referring webpage; browser used; date and time. This information may be collected to monitor your navigation of our webpages. We may use browser-IP-address information and anonymous-browser history to report information about site accesses and for profiling purposes. This information is generally used to improve web presentation and utilization. We also may use IP address information for troubleshooting purposes. These webpages may use "cookies" in order to deliver web content specific to individual’s web navigation interests, or to keep track of online transactions.
Disclosure of Collected Information
Whittier College will not disclose or share, without your consent, personally identifiable information to any nonaffiliated third party vendor, except for certain explicit circumstances in which disclosure may be required by law.
Updating Personal Information
Questions regarding your options to review, modify or delete previously provided personal information should be directed to the campus entity to which you provided the information.
Policy Changes
This privacy policy has been created and approved by Whittier College. Any revisions to this privacy policy will be posted at this URL. You may submit inquiries about this policy to publicrelations@whittier.edu.
Links to Other Sites
You may encounter links to webpages of entities not managed or maintained by Whittier College. Those webpages may have privacy policies that differ from this one. You also may encounter links to websites of organizations not directly affiliated with the Whittier College. Please be aware that Whittier College is not responsible for the information practices of external organizations. We recommend you review the privacy statements of each webpage that collects personal information.
Reporting Copyright Infringements
In accordance with Title II of the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (DMCA), Whittier has designated an agent to receive notification of a claim of copyright infringement for the Whittier College network domain, whittier.edu. Please see the Whittier College DMCA Policy to report a claim of copyright infringement.
Terms of Use
Breadcrumb
Home /
Terms of Use
